Let's hold hands, Penelope.
Yippee, yippee!
I'm going out to a walk!
Penelope is going out for a walk with her mom and dad.
Are you ready to go?
Yes!
Oh, wait, Penelope.
What is it, mom?
Let's leave Max at home.
You might leave him behind somewhere.
But I will be careful. I won't forget Max.
But you'll be upset if you lose him.
I want to take Max with me.
He's always with me when I sleep.
And when I eat meals.
Ah, wait a minute.
I've got an idea.
I'm a dear Penelope.
I want to know what I do, she has.
Can you guess?
If I put Max in my hat...
Mom and dad won't know.
Oh, she'll know.
I demand my jumper.
I can tell mom and dad that my tummy is too big, because I ate too much.
Maybe it's a good idea to put to me my trouser pockets.
Then my bottom won't touch when I get on the swings.
That's what I'll do.
Well, let's go Penelope.
Oh, mom.
Yes.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Be careful darling.
Yes, mom.
Oh, a puzzle.
Wow, it's fun.
Oh, dear Penelope.
Your shoes will get old, Muddy.
Look, let's hold hands.
With me too.
Yes.
Oh, I want to get Muddy.
What is it, Penelope?
Nothing.
I can't climb a tree holding hands.
It's no fun.
Yes, I've got an idea.
Oh dear, Penelope has another idea.
I wonder what it is this time.
If Max takes my place,
I bet Mum and Dad won't notice,
and they'll think that it's me.
Then I can have lots of fun.
You pee, you pee.
You pee.
Wow.
It's fun.
It's Muddy.
You pee.
Now I'll wipe my trousers and shoes with my scarf,
and there will be all clean,
and Mum and Dad won't notice.
It's so good.
What's the matter, Penelope?
I have a very good, wonderful idea.
Wonderful idea.
Will you share it?
It's a secret.
You've had a lot of funny ideas today.
Haven't you, Penelope?